<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bowen Memorial Methodist Church</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bowen Memorial Methodist Church</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 22:21:41 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Find Your Passion Through Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:05:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>All congregation members are encouraged to volunteer and serve the church. The opportunities available for serving include:&#xA;Serving at the Altar Ushering during the worship service Reading the Scripture during the worship service Sponsoring breakfast/snacks Collecting/counting offerings Teaching at Sunday School Participating in Praise and Worship Helping with media campaigns to promote church events Bowen Church also ministers in areas such as hospital visits, home visits for members who are sick and visits to slum areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a Member</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/membership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:18:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/membership/</guid>
      <description>To become a member of Bowen Memorial Methodist Church, fill up a membership application form available at the church vestry. Our Pastorate Committee will review this form and on approval, you will be included in the membership list.&#xA;Requirements You must be a Protestant Christian. You must attach your Baptism and Confirmation certificate along with the membership form. You must give a no-objection certificate or a transfer letter from your current church / parish, in case of transfer of membership from another church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service Timings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 22:21:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/</guid>
      <description> August 2025 Sunday, August 24&#xA;Sunday Service Time: 10:30 am – 12:00 pm Location: Bowen Memorial Methodist Church Address: WRFM+83R, Tulloch Rd, Apollo Bandar, Colaba, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India Description: Sunday Service Sunday, August 31&#xA;Gideon&amp;rsquo;s Sunday Time: 10:30 am – 12:00 pm Location: Bowen Memorial Methodist Church Address: WRFM+83R, Tulloch Rd, Apollo Bandar, Colaba, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India Description: Gideon&amp;rsquo;s Sunday </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15-Mar-2025 – On Value</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/15-mar-2025-on-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 02:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/15-mar-2025-on-value/</guid>
      <description>29 Are not two sparrows sold for a copper coin? And not one of them falls to the ground apart from your Father&amp;rsquo;s will. 30 But the very hairs of your head are all numbered. 31 Do not fear therefore; you are of more value than many sparrows. (Matthew 10:29-31)&#xA;In every situation and every circumstance of your life, God is always doing a thousand different things that you cannot see and do not know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily Meditation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/meditation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:49:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/meditation/</guid>
      <description>15-Mar-2025 – On Value Date: March 16, 2025&#xA;Tags: christ, faith, value&#xA;29 Are not two sparrows sold for a copper coin? And not one of them falls to the ground apart from your Father&amp;rsquo;s will. 30 But the very hairs of your head are all numbered.&#xA;Read More&#xA;16-Mar-2025 – On Assurance Date: March 16, 2025&#xA;Tags: assurance, christ, everlasting, faith, life, reaping&#xA;7 Do not be deceived, God is not mocked; for whatever a man sows, that he will also reap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16-Mar-2025 – On Assurance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/16-mar-2025-on-assurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 02:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/16-mar-2025-on-assurance/</guid>
      <description>7Do not be deceived, God is not mocked; for whatever a man sows, that he will also reap. 8For he who sows to his flesh will of the flesh reap corruption, but he who sows to the Spirit will of the Spirit reap everlasting life. 9And let us not grow weary while doing good, for in due season we shall reap if we do not lose heart… (Galatians 6:7-9)&#xA;My faith rests not in what I am or shall be, or feel, or know, but in what Christ is, in what he has done, and in what he is doing for me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>08-March-2025 – Godly Women</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/08-march-2025-godly-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:52:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/08-march-2025-godly-women/</guid>
      <description>Be an Esther, bold and courageous enough to stand for the truth, to voice your opinion and fight for the good of others, even when it means to sacrifice yourself. If God has put you in a position, it is for a purpose. Never be afraid to heed to that inner voice. Be a Ruth, loyal in all your relationships, walk the extra mile and don&amp;rsquo;t quit when things get tough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>08-March-2025 – On our Living Hope</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/08-march-2025-on-our-living-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:46:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/08-march-2025-on-our-living-hope/</guid>
      <description>Blessed be the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, which according to his abundant mercy hath begotten us again unto a lively hope by the resurrection of Jesus Christ from the dead. (1 Peter 1:3)&#xA;You can be born in a Christian home, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make you a Christian. — Billy Graham&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s Pray:&#xA;Lord, we praise You for the salvation You have provided through Your son. We are grateful for the living hope we have of Your imminent coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>07-March-2025 – On Confidence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/07-march-2025-on-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 03:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/07-march-2025-on-confidence/</guid>
      <description>Let us therefore come boldly unto the throne of grace, that we may obtain mercy, and find grace to help in time of need. - (Hebrews 4:16)&#xA;Prayer is the core of the day. Take prayer out, and the day would collapse. — Amy Carmichael&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s pray:&#xA;• Lord, give us the confidence to come closer to the Throne of grace today.&#xA;• Lord, we completely depend on you during a time of need today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>06-March-2025 – On God&#39;s Word</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/06-march-2025-on-gods-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 06:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/06-march-2025-on-gods-word/</guid>
      <description>For whatsoever things were written aforetime were written for our learning, that we through patience and comfort of the scriptures might have hope. (Romans 15:4)&#xA;As Christians, we have only one authority, one compass: the Word of God — Billy Graham&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s Pray:&#xA;• Precious Father, we praise you for your Word that you have provided for us today.&#xA;• Lord thank you for your Word, which is a compass in our day-to-day life today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Methodist Youth Fellowship</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/myf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 14:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/myf/</guid>
      <description>Youth Fellowship helps our young adults discover the plans and purposes God has for their lives in an environment specifically designed for them.&#xA;At Bowen Church, the MYF takes the lead in the Worship Ministry of the church. MYF, as a major initiative, hosts the Open Mic program every Friday.&#xA;On October 15, 2023, the MYF celebrated Youth Sunday with the youth conducting the service. We decided to theme the day as an Outreach service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PB&amp;J Open Mic: Celebrate Creativity &amp; Community 🎤</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pbj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pbj/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to PB&amp;amp;J (Praises Beyond Jam) Open Mic Night at Bowen Memorial Methodist Church!&#xA;Our open mic night is a vibrant and inclusive platform where individuals from all walks of life can come together to express their creativity, share their talents, and celebrate the joy of artistic expression.&#xA;📅 Event Details Event Details: 📅 Every Friday ⏰ 6:00 PM – 9:00 PM&#xA;📍 Tulloch Rd, Apollo Bandar, Colaba, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400001</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generosity in Action</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/giving/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/giving/</guid>
      <description>Your support means the world to us. If you wish to donate to the Ministry of the Bowen Memorial Methodist Church, you can use the following bank details. Every contribution, big or small, brings us one step closer to realizing our vision for our beloved church.&#xA;Bank Account Details Account Name: CRT MRC MC BOWEN M METHODIST CHURCH&#xA;Account Number: 316402010874316&#xA;Branch: Union Bank, Clare Road Branch&#xA;IFSC Code: UBIN0531642</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Methodist Beliefs and Values</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/beliefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/beliefs/</guid>
      <description>The Methodist branch of the Protestant religion traces its roots back to 1739 when it developed in England as the result of a revival and reform movement begun by John Wesley and his brother Charles. Wesley&amp;rsquo;s three basic precepts that launched the Methodist tradition were:&#xA;Shun evil and avoid partaking in wicked deeds at all costs. Be kind to one and another as much as possible. Abide by the teachings of God the Almighty Father.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birthdays and Anniversaries</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/birthdays-and-anniversaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:32:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/birthdays-and-anniversaries/</guid>
      <description>Members celebrating their birthdays and anniversaries in August 2025.&#xA;Birthdays 6th Aug – Mrs. Christian Mathews 6th Aug – Dr. Lawrence Massey 12th Aug – Ms. Jerusha Dashrathan Anniversaries None&#xA;May God bless everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bowen Herald: Your Source For Spiritual Insights &amp; Community News</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bowen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:29:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bowen/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The Bowen Herald,&amp;rdquo; your online source for insightful articles, uplifting stories, and community news. Published by Bowen Memorial Methodist Church, this digital bulletin is designed to keep you connected, informed, and inspired on your faith journey and within our vibrant community.&#xA;Discover Engaging Content: Explore various topics that cater to your spiritual growth, personal development, and community engagement. From thought-provoking reflections to updates on church events, &amp;ldquo;The Bowen Herald&amp;rdquo; offers diverse content that aims to enrich your life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serving and Growing Together</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ministries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ministries/</guid>
      <description>Sunday School Families are the pillars of our society. We are here to come alongside you as parents in the joys and trials of raising young children and to be a partner in preaching the gospel to the youngest generation. Our vision is that kids participate in worship for the Glory of our Lord Jesus Christ.&#xA;Sunday School begins at 11 AM during worship. Your children will be in a safe environment, with screened and trained teachers, where they will learn Biblical truth, sing songs, do activities, memorize scripture, and have a fun time doing it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
